I PUTU RADIKA BADRAGITHA

FRONT-END DEVELOPERS



CONTACT

0895-3556-2867-1

puturadika69@gmail.com

RadikaBadra

Denpasar, Bali

SKILLS

Web Development (JS, React.JS, VUE.JS)

Mobile Development (Flutter, React Native)

Databases Management (SQL)

Teamwork (Github, GIT)

UI Design (Figma, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop)

Critical Thinker

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree in Informatics Engineer

Primakara University

2021 - Present

Current GPA: 3.88/4.0

Computer Software Engineering

Vocational High School 1 Denpasar

2018 - 2021

LANGUAGES

Indonesia (Native)

English (Conversation)

PROFILE

I am an university student studying Informatics Engineering at Primakara University. I am willing to learn web development and mobile development. I am very interested in the IT industry and willing to work with discipline and responsibility from my experiences.

WORK EXPERIENCES

Benerin.id

September 2022-Present

Create an online technician service website using VUE.JS.

Denpasar, Bali, Indonesia

Taksu Tech

March 2020-April 2020

Experienced intern proficient in React Native for mobile app development and Laravel for backend services.

Denpasar, Bali, Indonesia

PT. Global Mertasari Digital

December 2019-January 2020

WordPress and SEO intern skilled in optimizing web projects for improved visibility and user experience.

Denpasar, Bali, Indonesia

COMMUNITY EXPERIENCES

GDSC Primakara University

September 2023-Present

Core Team (Tech Support)

Primakara Developers

October 2022-Present

Facilitator and Lead Facilitator